alignable.com 2014-07-02

# Privacy Policy

### Introduction:

The mission of Alignable is to connect the world’s local businesses and organizations to enable them to be more productive and successful. To achieve our Mission, we make services available through our website, mobile applications, and developer platform, to help you, your connections, and your community meet, exchange ideas, learn, make deals, or find opportunities and make decisions in a network of trusted relationships and groups. 

Being part of Alignable means sharing information about yourself with other individuals and businesses, communicating with them, as well as working privately on your own. By default, your account is set up to share the information that we have found the vast majority of our Users are interested in sharing. But the amount and type of information you decide to share, and with whom you share it, is up to you. 

Here are the three main types of information on Alignable: 

_Information about yourself that you share._ This is the information that your connections, other businesses, and organizations see about you. This includes your profile and your contributions to discussions on Alignable Groups, Answers, or other community features Alignable may offer such as “Profile Stats” which, if you choose to opt-in, can show you who viewed your profile (and will show others when you visited their profiles). **You have control over what you share, and you can update information at any time.**

_Communication._ We help you communicate with connections and other businesses and organizations. Some of this is one-to-one, some of it is in groups, and some of it is public discussion. **You decide how much or how little you wish to communicate to individuals or groups.**

_Private activity._ We also provide tools that you can use privately on Alignable (for example, searching, or adding notes to your connections information.) **These actions and information are private and we don't share or distribute them to others on the website.**

Of course, maintaining your trust is our top concern, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy: 

We do not rent, sell, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent, except as described in this policy or as required by law 

We do not share any information you have not chosen to display on your Alignable profile to other parties, unless compelled by law, or as necessary to enforce our User Agreement or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Alignable, its Users, and the public 

All information that you provide will be protected with industry standard protocols and technology. 

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by means of a notice on our home page so that you may access and review the changes to this document in advance of your continued use of the service. If you object to any changes, you may close your account. By continuing to use the Alignable service after notice of changes has been sent to you or published on the Alignable website, you are consenting to the changes. 

**Please read this policy** and send us questions, concerns and suggestions [email support.](mailto:support@alignable.com)

### What Alignable’s Privacy Policy Covers:

  1. Information collected by Alignable. 
  2. How Alignable uses your information. 
  3. Your information choices. 
  4. Your obligations as a User. 
  5. Important information regarding service eligibility and US Department of Commerce Safe Harbor certification. 
  6. Security. 
  7. How to contact us. 

### 1\. Information Collected

The mission of Alignable is to connect the world’s local businesses and organizations to enable them to be more productive and successful. To achieve our Mission, we make services available through our website, mobile applications, and developer platform, premium services, and other information provided as part of the Alignable services (“Services”) to enable you, your connections, and your community to meet, exchange ideas, learn, make deals, or find opportunities, create, share, and distribute information in collaboration with one another, and make decisions in a network of trusted relationships and groups. 

By joining Alignable, you voluntarily and willingly provide Alignable Corporation in Boston MA, USA certain information, including personally identifiable information, which we collect in order to provide the Services. If you have any hesitation about providing information to us and/or having your information displayed on the Alignable website or otherwise used in any manner permitted in this Privacy Policy and the User Agreement, you should not become a member of the Alignable community; and, if you are already a member, you should close your account. 

We collect your personal information in the following ways: 

  1. **Registration:** In order to become a User, you must provide us the following information to create an account: name, email address, business, address, country, and password. Without this minimal amount of information, you cannot create aAlignable account. Like other passwords, you should choose one that is known only by you. Alignable requests other information from you during the registration process, (e.g., industry, location, etc.) that Alignable uses to provide better, more customized services such as language-specific profile pages and updates, better ads, and more valuable marketing opportunities. You acknowledge that this information is personal to you, and by creating an account on Alignable; you allow others, including Alignable, to identify you and to allow LI to use your information in accordance with our User Agreement.

  2. **Profile Information:** Once you become a User, you may provide additional information to your Alignable Profile describing your interests, business history, background, recommendations from other Alignable Users, group memberships, and networking objectives (among other options). Providing additional information about yourself beyond what is minimally required at registration is entirely up to you, but providing additional information enables you to derive more benefit from Alignable and your business network by helping you build your local business identity and leverage your network and facilitating your search for marketing partners, resources, information, and new opportunities. Any information you provide at registration or in the Profile section may be used by Alignable as described in the User Agreement and this Privacy Policy, including for the purpose of allowing marketing opportunities to find you on Alignable, or for serving more relevant advertisements on Alignable. Learn more about Alignable’s advertising practices by reading this privacy policy, in particular Sections 1.H, 2.J, and 2.K. If you decide not to share certain information, you may not receive the full benefit of being a Alignable User. 

  3. **Contacts Information:** In order to connect with others on Alignable, you may use the Services to send invitations either to their Alignable profiles or email addresses of people you know if they have not registered with Alignable. The names and email addresses of people whom you invite will be used to send your invitations and reminders as well as to allow Alignable to help expand your network. Please note that when you send an invitation to connect to another User, that User will have access to your email address because it is displayed in the invitation. Your Alignable connections will also have access to your email address. You may not invite anyone you do not know and trust to connect with you. 

You may also choose to manually enter or upload data about your contacts to the “Contacts” section of your account on Alignable. Information entered into Contacts is only viewable by you. By providing email addresses or other information of non-Users to Alignable, you represent that you have authority to do so. All information that you enter or upload about your contacts is covered by the User Agreement and this Privacy Policy and will enable us to provide customized services such as suggesting people to connect with on Alignable. 

  4. **Customer Service:** We collect information when you interact with Alignable’s website in order to accurately categorize and respond to customer inquiries and investigate breaches of our terms. 

  5. **Using the Alignable Site and Applications:** We receive information when you interact with and use the Alignable website, Alignable Applications (e.g. Alignable for iPhone, Android, etc.), and Alignable platform technology (such as “Share on Alignable” plugins for publishers). For example, we know when you click on ads, upload content, join groups, participate in polls, install aAlignable mobile application, share content on Alignable, etc. 

  6. **Using Third Party Services and Visiting Third Party Sites:** We receive information when you use your Alignable account to log in or authenticate to a third-party website or application. Also, if you are logged into Alignable and visit a third party site that embeds Alignable professional plugins, like “Share on Alignable” for web publishers, Alignable will receive information that those pages have loaded in your web browser. Alignable will use this information to personalize the Alignable-provided functionality, including providing you insights from your Alignable network, allowing you to share information with your network, enabling you to use Alignable functionality off the Alignable site and serving you more relevant advertising. Users wishing to disable this personalization may [opt-out](mailto:support@alignable.com?subject=Opt-out%20%20Third%20Party%20Services) of this feature. Alignable’s retention of this data is addressed in Section 1.K. 

  7. **Cookies:** Like most websites, we use cookies and web log files to track site usage and trends, to improve the quality of our service, to customize your experience on Alignable, as well as to deliver Alignable and third-party advertising to Users both on and off the Alignable site. A cookie is a tiny data file that resides on your computer, mobile phone, or other device, and allows us to recognize you as a User when you return to the Alignable website using the same computer and web browser. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser, but in some cases doing so may impact your ability to use Alignable. One type of cookie, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you’ve logged in to your Alignable account. The next time you visit the Alignable website, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing User so you will not need to log in before using the Services. In order to access or change any of your private information (like a credit card number) or to send a message to another User, however, you must log in securely again with your password even if your computer contains your persistent cookie. Another type of cookie, called a “session” cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the Alignable website. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser. Other technology like Macromedia’s flash can be used to place the functional equivalent of a cookie on your computer. You can control flash “local stored objects” or “flash cookies” using the Macromedia Website Privacy Settings Panel at www.macromedia.com. Alignable may use cookie-equivalent technology for the limited purpose of enhancing the security of Alignable's services. We do not use flash cookies for advertising purposes. 

In the course of serving advertisements or optimizing the Services to our Users, we may allow authorized third parties to place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Any information provided to third parties through cookies will not be personally identifiable but may provide general segment information (e.g., your industry or geography, career field, or information about your professional or educational background) for the enhancement of your user experience by providing more relevant advertising. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Alignable does not store unencrypted personally identifiable information in the cookies. 

  8. **Advertising and Web Beacons:** To support the Services we provide at no cost to our Users, as well as provide a more relevant and useful experience for our Users, we target and serve our own ads and third-party ads both on and off the site using ad networks. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad exchanges, ad technology vendors and research firms. 

We target ads to Users based on general profile categories (e.g., “product managers in Texas”) or on non-personally identifiable information inferred from a User’s profile (e.g., industry, current or former business, years in business, nationality, or other aspects of your life) in addition to a User’s use of Alignable or their clicking on Alignable ad inventory. Alignable does not provide personally identifiable information to any third party ad network. 

We use ad technology such as web beacons, pixels, anonymous ad network tags, and cookies to more effectively serve ads to our Users on and off Alignable through ad networks, as well as to collect anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for advertisers. Because your web browser requests advertisements and web beacons directly from ad network servers, these networks can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site. 

You may opt-out of ads served to you off Alignable [here](mailto:support@alignable.com?subject=Opt-out%20Ads) , by turning off “Advertising Preferences.” If you opt-out you may lose certain functionality of the Alignable Services, as well as the potential benefit of receiving ads that are targeted to your interests which, in turn, may limit your ability to fully realize the benefits of the Alignable Services to build and leverage your professional network. 

  9. **Log files, IP Addresses and information about your computer and mobile device:** Due to the communications standards on the internet, when you visit the Alignable website we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave Alignable. Additionally, advertisers receive the URL of the page you were on when you click on an ad on Alignable. Alignable also receives the internet protocol (“IP”) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, email patterns, your mobile device (including your UDID) and mobile operating system (if you are accessing Alignable using a mobile device), as well as the name of your ISP or your mobile carrier. Alignable may also receive location data passed to it from third-party services or GPS-enabled devices that you have enabled. Also, as described above in Sections 1.E. and 1.F., Alignable receives information when you access web pages containing Alignable interactive plugins, such as “Share on Alignable” or “Connect with Alignable” functionality. You can control the collection and use of this information here. The link between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties without your permission, except as described in Section 2.L (“Compliance with Legal Process”), below. 

  10. **Rights to Access, Correct and Eliminate Information About You:** You have a right to access, modify, correct and eliminate the data you supplied to Alignable. If you update any of your information, we may keep a copy of the information that you originally provided to us in our archives for uses documented in this policy. You may request deletion of your information at any time by [contacting Alignable customer service.](mailto:support@alignable.com?subject=Delete%20my%20archived%20data) We will respond to your request within 30 days. Please note, however that information you have shared with others, or that other Users have copied, may also remain visible even if you request its deletion. 

  11. **Data Retention:** Alignable will retain your information for so long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, except in the case of our professional plugin impression data, which we de-identify after 12 months. If you wish to close your account, you may do so [here.](mailto:support@alignable.com?subject=Close%20my%20account) We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce this Agreement. 

### 2\. Uses of personal information

  1. **Consent to Alignable Processing Information About You:** The information you provide to Alignable may reveal, or allow others to identify, your nationality, ethnic origin, gender, age, and other aspects of your life. By providing information to us for the purposes of creating your User account or adding any additional details to your Alignable profile, you are expressly and voluntarily accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and Alignable’s User Agreement that allow Alignable to process information about you. Supplying information to Alignable, including any information deemed “sensitive” by applicable law, is entirely voluntary on your part. You have the right to withdraw your consent to Alignable’s collection and processing of your information at any time, in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy and the User Agreement, by changing your Settings, or by [closing your account](mailto:support@alignable.com?subject=Close%20my%20account) , but please note that your withdrawal of consent will not be retroactive. 

  2. **Alignable Communications:** As described in the User Agreement, we will communicate with you through email, notices posted on the Alignable website, messages to your Alignable inbox, or through other means available through the service, including mobile text messages. We may send you a series of emails that help inform new Users about the features of the Services, and we will also send you service messages relating to the functioning of the Services. We may also send you messages with promotional information directly or on behalf of our partners, unless you have opted out of receiving promotional information. 

You can change your e-mail and contact preferences at any time by logging into your account and changing your settingsrelated to your email notification choices. If you wish, you can also opt-out of receiving promotional emails by sending a [request](mailto:support@alignable.com?subject=Opt-out%20promotional%20emails) to Alignable customer service. 

Please be aware that you cannot opt-out of receiving service messages from Alignable. Also, if we send communications to you via the carrier service with which you have a mobile communications subscription or otherwise have access, you understand you will pay any service fees associated with your receipt of messages on your mobile device (including text messaging charges). 

  3. **User Communications:** Many communications you initiate through Alignable (e.g., an invitation sent to a non-User) will list your primary email address and name in the header of the message. Messages you initiate may also provide aggregate information about your network (for instance how many people are in your network), but will not list the people to whom you’re directly connected. Other communications that you initiate through the Alignable website, like a request for an introduction, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal email address contact information. Your contact information will only be shared with another User if both of you have indicated that you would like to establish contact with each other. 

  4. **Customized Content:** We use information you provide to us (or to third parties with whom Alignable offers combined services) to customize your experience on our website. For example, when you login to your account, we will display the names of new Users who have recently joined your network or recent status updates from your connections. 

  5. **Sharing Information with Third Parties:** Alignable takes the privacy of our Users very seriously, and we do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to third parties, except as described in this policy. We will also not share other personal information not published to your profile or generated through engagement with other Alignable services (Groups, Joins, Company Pages, etc.) without your explicit consent or to carry out your instructions (for example, to process payment information) unless, disclosure is reasonably necessary in our opinion to: (1) comply with legal process, including, but not limited to, civil and criminal subpoenas, court orders or other compulsory disclosures; (2) enforce this Agreement; (3) respond to claims of a violation of the rights of third parties, whether or not the third party is a User, individual, or government agency; (4) respond to customer service inquiries; or (5) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Alignable, our Users or the public. 

Alignable offers a “public profile” feature that allows Users to publish portions of their Alignable profile to the public internet. This public profile will be crawled by and displayed through search engines when someone searches for your name. You may opt-out of this feature by editing your account settings; however, Alignable does not warrant how often third-party search engines will update their caches, which may contain old public profile information. 

Content distributed through Alignable’s sharing features and third party integrations may result in displaying some of your information outside of Alignable. For example, when you post content to aAlignable Group that is open for public discussion, your content, including your name as the contributor, may be displayed in search engine results. Or, if you have bound your Alignable account to your Twitter account, you can easily share content into both Alignable as well as to Twitter. 

We may provide aggregated anonymous data about the usage of the Services to third parties for purposes that we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate, including to prospective advertisers on Alignable. 

  6. **Developers using Alignable Platform Services:** We collaborate with and allow third parties to use Alignable’s developer platform to offer services and functionality in conjunction with and outside of Alignable. These third parties are either partners (“Alignable Partners”) with whom we have negotiated an agreement to provide services (“Combined Services”), for example, InApps, or developers (“Platform Developers”) who have agreed to our developer terms in order to build applications (“Platform Applications”). Both the negotiated agreements and our API terms and conditions contain restrictions on access, storage and use of your information. 

If you choose to use Combined Services or a Platform Application, you may be asked to confirm acceptance of the privacy policy and/or user agreement of the Alignable Partner or Platform Developer, which have not necessarily been reviewed or approved by Alignable. It is your choice whether or not to make use of Combined Services or Platform Applications and whether to proceed under any third party terms, and once you do, the third party's terms, and not this policy, will govern how they handle information you provide to them directly or through your Alignable account. 

Also, despite our agreements and technical steps taken to restrict access to and avoid possible misuse of information, we may not screen or audit all Combined Services or Platform Applications. We also cannot guarantee that any Alignable Partner or Platform Developer will abide by our agreement. You agree that your use of Combined Services or Platform Applications is on an “as is” basis and without any warranty. 

If you use any Combined Service or Platform Application, the Alignable Partner or Platform Developer may access and share certain information about you, such as non-public profile information and information visible only to your connections. This includes information about your connections by virtue of you being connected to others. However, unless you have used a Combined Service or Platform Application, it can only access the information about you that is otherwise visible to other Alignable Users. 

To revoke permission granted to a Combined Service or Platform Application at any time, please visit the settings page. If the relevant Platform Developer or Application, or Alignable Partner is not listed under Authorized Applications, go directly to the Application Details page for the Platform Application you wish to uninstall. Note, however, that even if you revoke the permission granted a third party, your connections, other members of your network, or other Users of Alignable may still be using the Platform Application, so the Platform Application or Combined Service may still have access to certain information about you, just as those Users do. You may opt-out of providing information to third parties through others connected to you by [contacting support.](mailto:support@alignable.com?subject=Opt-out%20third%20party%20data%20sharing%20through%20connections) To report any suspected misuse of information, contact Alignable’s customer service. Alignable is not responsible for your use of or inability to use any Combined Service or Platform Application, including the content, accuracy, or reliability of applications and the privacy practices or other policies of Alignable Partners or Platform Developers. 

  7. **Polls and Surveys:** Polls and Surveys may be conducted by Alignable, Alignable Users or third parties. As a User, you may be invited to participate in polls and surveys from the Alignable website. Your selection may be random, or it may be based on your non-personally identifiable information, such as job title, geography, company size and/or industry. Whether or not you decide to participate in a poll or survey is completely up to you. 

After you complete a poll, you will be given access to the aggregate responses of the poll on a results page. Some third parties may target advertisements to you on the results page based on your answers in the poll. Further, Alignable or third parties may follow up with you via Alignable Messaging regarding your participation unless you have opted out of receiving messages. 

We may use third parties to deliver incentives to you to participate in surveys or polls. If the delivery of incentives requires your contact information, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information to the third party fulfilling the incentive offer, which will only be used for the purpose of delivering incentives and/or verifying your contact information. It is up to you whether you provide this information, or whether you desire to take advantage of an incentive. 

We will not disclose any personally identifiable information to any third parties in connection with the conduct of any polls or surveys. Your consent to use any personally identifiable information for the purposes set forth in the poll or survey will be explicitly requested by the party conducting it. 

  8. **Search:** We offer search services to help find information and learn more about other Users (for example, you can search for Users with particular interests or marketing experience, or that you may know from your community or profession), as well as marketing opportunities. Alignable search also allows Users to find marketing opportunities, companies, and contributions to the community aspects of the Alignable Services, such as Groups and Answers that will help Users more effectively use Alignable and expand their network. We use information from User profiles and contributions to Groups, Company Pages, and Answers to inform and refine our search service. 

  9. **Answers, Groups, and other Services:** If you post on the Answers section of Alignable, participate in Alignable Groups, or import a blog, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you choose to provide there can be read, collected, or used by other Users of these forums, as well as Platform Developers and other third parties, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. Alignable is not responsible for the information you choose to submit in these forums. Also, some content in Alignable Groups may be public and searchable on the internet if the Group owner has opened the group for public discussions. You can delete your posts to Answers and Alignable Groups at any time. However, please note that ideas you post and information you share may be seen and used by other Users, and Alignable cannot guarantee that other Users have not made copies of or use the ideas and information that you share with others on Alignable. 

  10. **Testimonials and Advertisements Placed through Alignable Ads Service:** If you provide any testimonials about the Alignable Services or place advertisements through the Alignable Ads, we may post those testimonials and examples of advertisements you place in connection with our promotion of these services to third parties. Testimonials and advertisements may include your name and other personal information that you have provided. 

  11. **Advertising and Endorsements on Alignable:** In order to deliver relevant and valuable ads to you and your network, Alignable may use your name and profile photo in connection with social advertising based on content shared on Alignable. This advertising may include the fact that you have recommended or endorsed a product or service on Alignable, connected with a company, joined Groups or conversations, established or added content to your profile, etc., and will only be displayed to your Alignable network. You can opt-out of allowing your name and/or profile photo to be used in social ads [here.](mailto:support@alignable.com?subject=Opt-out%20name%20and%20profile%20photo%20in%20social%20ads)

  12. **Compliance with Legal Process:** It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information, profile information and/or information about your activities as a Alignable User when required by subpoena or other legal process, or if Alignable has a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (a) investigate, prevent or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities or to assist government enforcement agencies; (b) to enforce the User Agreement, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations, or to protect the security or integrity of our site; and/or (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property or personal safety of Alignable, our Users, employees, or others. 

  13. **Disclosures to Others as the Result of a Change in Control or Sale of Alignable Corporation:** We may also disclose your personal information and other information you provide to another third party as part of a sale of the assets of Alignable Corporation, a subsidiary or division, or as the result of a change in control of the company. Any third party to which Alignable transfers or sells Alignable’s assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that you provide to us. 

### 3\. Your Information Choices

  1. **Accessing and Changing Your Account Information:** You can review the personal information you provided to us and make any desired changes to the information you publish, or to the settings for your Alignable account including your email and contact preferences, at any time by logging in to your account on the Alignable website. Please be aware that even after your request for a change is processed, Alignable may, for a time, retain residual information about you in its backup and/or archival copies of its database. 

  2. **Default Settings:** Because the mission of Alignable is to connect the world’s local businesses to enable them to become more productive and successful, we have established what we believe to be reasonable default settings that we have found most professionals desire. Because Users may use and interact with Alignable in a variety of ways, and because those uses may change over time, we designed our settings to provide our users granular control over the information they share. We encourage our Users to review their account settings and adjust them in accordance with their preferences. 

Alignable accounts are also defaulted to allow Users to be contacted to participate in polls, surveys and partner advertising. [Contact support](mailto:support@alignable.com) to change these settings. 

  3. **Closing Your Account:** You can close your account through the Alignable customer service site. If you close your Alignable account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable database. If you close your account, we have no obligation to retain your information, and may delete any or all of your account information without liability. However, we may retain certain data contributed by you if Alignable believes it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. Alignable may also retain and use your information if necessary to provide the Services to other Users. For example, just as an email you may send to another person through an email service provider resides in that person’s inbox even after you delete it from your sent files or close your account, emails or Alignable Messages you send on Alignable to other Users, as well as your contributions to Alignable Answers or Groups, may remain visible to others after you have closed your account. Similarly, other information you have shared with others, or that other Users have copied, may also remain visible. Alignable disclaims any liability in relation to the deletion or retention (subject to the terms herein) of information or any obligation not to delete the information. Alignable does not control when search engines update their cache, which may contain certain public profile information that has since been removed from Alignable’s publicly viewable database. 

  4. **Memorializing Accounts:** If we learn that a User or business is no longer in business, we may memorialize the User’s account. In these cases we may restrict profile access, remove messaging functionality, and close an account if we receive a formal request from the User or other proper legal request to do so. 

### 4\. Your Obligations

As a User, you have certain obligations to other Users. Some of these obligations are imposed by applicable law and regulations, and others have become commonplace in user-friendly communities of like-minded members such as Alignable: 

You must, at all times, abide by the terms and conditions of the then-current Privacy Policy and User Agreement. This includes respecting all intellectual property rights that may belong to third parties (such as trademarks or photographs). 

You must not download or otherwise disseminate any information that may be deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, racist or xenophobic, or which may otherwise violate the purpose and spirit of Alignable and its community of Users. 

You must not provide to Alignable and/or other Users information that you believe might be injurious or detrimental to your person or to your professional or social status. 

You must keep your username and password confidential and not share it with others. 

Any violation of these guidelines may lead to the restriction, suspension or termination of your account at the sole discretion of Alignable. 

### 5\. Important information

Children and Minors - **Children under the age of 18 are not eligible to use our service.**

### 6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy at any time, with or without advance notice. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, or in the Privacy Policy document itself, we will display a notice on the Alignable website or send you an email, so that you may review the changed terms prior to continuing to use the site. As always, if you object to any of the changes to our terms, and you no longer wish to use Alignable, you may [close your account.](mailto:support@alignable.com) Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that Alignable has about you and your account. Using the Alignable Services after a notice of changes has been sent to you or published on our site shall constitute consent to the changed terms or practices. 

### 7\. Security

In order to help secure your personal information, access to your data on Alignable is password-protected, and sensitive data (such as credit card information) is protected by SSL encryption when it is exchanged between your web browser and the Alignable website. To protect any data you store on our servers, Alignable also regularly audits its system for possible vulnerabilities and attacks, and we use a tier-one secured-access data center. However, since the internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Alignable. There is no guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information. Please note that emails, instant messaging, and similar means of communication with other Users of Alignable are not encrypted, and we strongly advise you not to communicate any confidential information through these means. 

### 8\. How to contact us

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us [here](mailto:support@alignable.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20questions) or contact us at: 

Alignable Corporation

Attn: Legal Department, Privacy Policy Issues

60 Thoreau Street

Suite 263

Concord, MA 01742-2411
